const kubrickQuestions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'What was the publication Kubrick was a photographer for?',
        options: ['People', 'Life', 'Look', 'The New Yorker'],
        answer: 'Look'
    }, {
        id: 2,
        question: 'Where in England did Kubrick live?',
        options: ['York', 'Oxford', 'Childwickbury', 'London'],
        answer: 'Childwickbury'
    }, {
        id: 3,
        question: `What was Kubrick's first feature film?`,
        options: ['Fear and Desire', 'The Killing', `Killer's Kiss`, 'Paths of Glory'],
        answer: 'Fear and Desire'
    }, {
        id: 4,
        question: 'What is the title of the book The Killing is based on?',
        options: [`What's the Point?`, 'The Track Job', 'Race Heist', 'Clean Break'],
        answer: 'Clean break'
    }, {
        id: 5,
        question: 'What horror film was Stanley offered to direct?',
        options: ['The Exorcist', 'Last House on the Left', 'Alien', 'Carrie'],
        answer: 'The Exorcist'
    }, {
        id: 6,
        question: 'What kind of media did Kubrick develop for the book I Stole $16,000,000?',
        options: ['Film', 'Radio Show', 'Sitcom', 'Short Film'],
        answer: 'Sitcom'
    }, {
        id: 7,
        question: `Which director sent a fan letter to Kubrick that meant so much to Kubrick, 
        he took so long to write a response that the director died before receiving the response?`,
        options: ['Ingmar Bergman', 'Federico Fellini', 'Akira Kurosawa', 'Andrei Tarkovsky'],
        answer: 'Akira Kurosawa'
    }, {
        id: 8,
        question: `Which director had lengthy conversations with Kubrick on the phone but when asking 
        Kubrick about his own movie-making secrets, Kubrick acted like he couldn't talk?`,
        options: ['Ingmar Bergman', 'Federico Fellini', 'Akira Kurosawa', 'Andrei Tarkovsky'],
        answer: 'Federico Fellini'
    }, {
        id: 9,
        question: `Which foreign director's films did Kubrick describe as unearthly and brilliant in his fan
        letter to the director?`,
        options: ['Ingmar Bergman', 'Federico Fellini', 'Akira Kurosawa', 'Andrei Tarkovsky'],
        answer: 'Ingmar Bergman'
    }, {
        id: 10,
        question: `Which actor is notorious for requiring the least amount of takes of Kubrick's collaborators?`,
        options: ['Jack Nicholson', 'Matthew Modine', 'Nicole Kidman', 'R. Lee Emery'],
        answer: 'R. Lee Emery'
    }, {
        id: 11,
        question: 'What film did Kubrick meet his wife Christiane on?',
        options: ['The Killing', 'Spartacus', 'Paths of Glory', 'Fear and Desire'],
        answer: 'Paths of Glory'
    }, {
        id: 12,
        question: `Which of these was NOT a potential project for Stanley Kubrick?`,
        options: ['Napoleon', 'Artificial Intelligence', 'Aryan Papers', 'Blade Runner'],
        answer: 'Blade Runner'
    }, {
        id: 13,
        question: `Which band requested that Kubrick direct them in a film?`,
        options: ['The Rolling Stones', 'The Monkeys', 'The Beatles', 'Pink Floyd'],
        answer: 'The Beatles'
    }, {
        id: 14,
        question: `What book did The Beatles want to adapt and have Kubrick direct?`,
        options: ['The Sun also Rises', 'The Great Gatsby', 'The Lord of the Rings', '1984'],
        answer: 'The Lord of the Rings'
    }, {
        id: 15,
        question: `Who acted in The Shining, A Clockwork Orange, and Barry Lyndon?`,
        options: ['Philip Stone', 'Leon Vitali', 'Steven Berkoff', 'Patrick Magee'],
        answer: 'Philip Stone'
    }, {
        id: 16,
        question: `Who acted in Eyes Wide Shut and Barry Lyndon?`,
        options: ['Philip Stone', 'Leon Vitali', 'Steven Berkoff', 'Patrick Magee'],
        answer: 'Leon Vitali'
    }, {
        id: 17,
        question: `Who in Stanley's family has appeared in 3 of his films?`,
        options: ['Vivian', 'Christiane', 'Anya', 'Katherina'],
        answer: 'Vivian'
    }
]

export default kubrickQuestions